[rock music playing]
WE WERE FRIENDS, EPISODE 4
[exhales sharply]
[chuckles]
He's not gonna look for it.
Math isn't going on the web novel website
and searching
for We Were Friends just to
check this.
He never would.
[inhales sharply, sighs]
[chuckles]
PAZER WEB NOVEL PORTAL
WE WERE FRIENDS
WE WERE FRIENDS, EPISODE 4
…YOON ONLY HAD EYES FOR TAE-HA…
[scoffs]
This girl is something else.
[sighs]
WE WERE FRIENDS, EPISODE 1
WE WERE FRIENDS, EPISODE 2
WE WERE FRIENDS, EPISODE 3
END OF EPISODE 3
CHAPTER 23: YOUR ROUGH THOUGHTS
AND ANXIOUS LOOKS
[Woo-su chewing] Mmm. Mmm.
EPISODE 7
So, it turns out that the EBC people
are very excited about the math class too.
[Gi-jeon, Dong-ju chuckling]
No wonder. I'd be excited too.
I mean, it's the elite math genius' class.
-[chuckles] Isn't that right? Right?
-Mm-hmm. Mmm.
Of course, I respect your decision.
You don't have to feel burdened at all.
-Not at all.
-Mmm! That's right.
But you're human,
and maybe you changed your mind, right?
So, let me ask one last time,
did you perhaps change your mind…
Uh, no?
[door closes]
-Do something.
-[Gi-jeon groans]
[Young-hee] Today's the day.
Therefore, I'm going to ask you
that until the filming is over
and until EBC production crew
leaves the school,
please stay focused
and refrain from saying anything
that may work against our school.
And I will ask,
especially the homeroom teachers,
to please make sure
you keep the students attire
and behavior under control.
That way, we will have successful
and smooth results!
-[teacher 1] Yes, ma'am.
-[teacher 2] Yes, ma'am.
Good luck, especially to our new teachers,
and the hero of this event,
Mr. Ga Woo-su.
♪ Good luck, Mr. Ga Woo-su ♪
-Yes.
-Please do a good job.
You can do it!
Mr. Da-ju, are you sure about this?
Yes, all roads lead to Seoul.
Isn't that right, ma'am?
Mmm. [chuckles]
-Auntie, Auntie!
-[cheers]
Here comes our main character.
Wow, Mr. E-den.
Look at that outfit. [gasps]
Wow. You are born for the spotlight, huh?
-Mr. Da-ju, I can always rely on you.
-[chuckling]
-Yes.
-Good.
Mmm.
So you're our dear principal's nephew.
[chuckles]
-[chuckles]
-[scoffs]
[door opens, closes]
[scoffs]
Auntie, you do know what the highlight
of this shoot is, right?
It's my flute solo.
Up on stage, and the curtains open.
Then a spotlight hits me perfectly.
Ha. Then that's it. It's game over.
-Sure, but drink this first. [chuckles]
-Okay.
-Huh.
-What?
[stammers]
-This is one of my favorite coffee shops.
-Yes, I know.
Drink it up.
Uh-huh. A little more. More.
A little more. More. More.
[winces]
[students chattering]
-[imitates flute]
-I like that.
What if I go on TV and become too popular
to be a teacher?
-[laughs]
-[laughing] Oh, my god.
Did you see how the newbies
got all dressed up for the shoot?
[scoffs] Pathetic.
All that preparation just to be
in a tiny corner of the background on TV.
I feel really bad for them, though.
-Exactly.
-[chuckles]
Uh, this is not working fast enough.
Huh? What was that?
[exhales sharply] Oh.
[gasps] I shouldn't waste time here.
I better go out and rehearse
with the cameras.
[sighs, gasps]
Oh…
I'm really sorry, E-den.
Film him without knowing?
[sighs]
Don't put it that way. It sounds illegal.
You'll just hit this button here
and turn the power on.
And this thing
will automatically start filming him.
I can't.
I could never do that. [sighs]
I've gotta keep a low profile, okay?
If I cause any more trouble,
I'll end up serving time.
Mm-mmm. Mmm. Mmm. Mm-hmm.
Come on, sit down. Sit down.
-[sighs]
-Come on, I get how mean Ga Woo-su is,
but he's not sending a student to jail.
And you need to do this to make up
for messing around in my class.
The nerve you had
to write that in my class.
Do you even know how hurt I was?
Th-That… [sighs]
I'm really sorry about that, but…
Of all the students here,
do you not get why I'm doing this?
Nope.
Well, if you don't do it…
we'll all be fired.
Do you get it?
You're getting fired?
This is a direct order from the principal.
Do you know what happens
when someone goes against her will?
We get fired.
And for me? "Not a problem."
[inhales sharply]
But…
it will be a problem for the PE
and Korean lit teachers.
What about them?
What would happen to them?
It won't be easy for Mr. Jung
to get hired given his leg issue.
Oh, and Mr. Yoon… Yeah…
Oh…
That's not good at all.
-That's right. It's not good.
-[sighs]
And…
I know everything, kid.
-Know what?
-Come on, you know what.
Do you have any idea how fast I caught on?
I could tell right away. [scoffs]
Did you actually think
you could hide it? [scoffs]
Well, I don't quite follow. [chuckles]
I knew about it all.
From the beginning.
Yeah, your rough thoughts
and anxious looks.
[scoffs] Mmm. I knew it all.
[inhales sharply]
I won't say a word
if you do the filming.
Okay?
[sighs] How did he find out
I write novels?
Girls, girls, girls.
What's all this chatter?
You know what's going on.
We're shooting the TV show.
[audio speeds up]
You're the faces
of Murim Girls' High School.
Come on, girls!
I can't believe not even one of you is…
[audio speeds up]
All right, do one of your Spanish lessons.
And you, solve some math problems.
Isn't that fun?
Dear?
Dear.
Ji-a.
Thank you, Jenny.
And your uniform?
-It's in the wash.
-Why?
Why did you have to wash it
when you obviously knew
you had to come to school?
I spilled oil on it.
You should have worn it
even if you had oil on it.
Or you should have just taken it out
from the washing machine
and worn it even if it was still wet.
Why today of all days?
And your gym clothes?
Don't have them.
Borrow them from someone else!
Actually, no.
No, that won't do. Hey, what's your name?
Choi Ji-a.
Follow me with your desk.
Move it. You're going slow.
We don't have time.
What's going on?
Oh…
Mr. Ga. Uh…
Well, you see, I'm going to have her
study alone in the counseling room
until the fifth period.
-Come on, grab your desk.
-[Woo-su] Go back in.
Mr. Ga.
Could I have a word
with you, please? [chuckles]
You know, EBC is coming here
to film their show today.
This lazy girl dozes off
during class all the time
and she's not wearing her uniform.
I know that's her thing.
[clicks tongue, inhales sharply]
But if she's going to ruin
this school's reputation on our big day,
she's better off not here.
I would freak out if they show her
on camera dressed like that.
I don't think this TV show
is worth making a student invisible.
Wow, you're kind of naive,
you know that, Mr. Ga?
TV shows are all scripted anyway.
Just until fifth period, okay?
Dear.
If you insist on removing her
from the show,
I won't let any of my students
participate in the filming.
[scoffs]
Who are you to say that?
[inhales sharply] Mr. Ga.
I believe I've explained this enough
for you to understand by now.
Come on.
Move!
[Young-hee sighs]
[Young-hee breathes shakily]
[straining]
Oh, no.
[gasps]
I'll talk to you later, Mr. Ga. [chuckles]
Yes, hi. I'm coming. [chuckles]
Back inside. Everyone sit down.
[pop music playing]
CHAPTER 24:
OUR SCHOOL RIGHT NOW
Hi, I'm Jenny.
And I'm on an exchange student program
in Murim Girls' High School.
Oh, I'm also from Singapore.
Um, why did you choose Murim Girls' High?
Oh, okay.
So Murim Girls' High School
is super famous in Singapore.
Internationally too, it's known to be
like a really good school.
[chuckles] Uh, brag about our school? Uh…
Yeah. Yeah, we have…
We have a really nice schoolyard.
And… And our teachers…
Our teachers are super, super handsome.
-Yep, that's for real.
-Mr. Yoon Dong-ju.
There's a teacher named Jung Gi-jeon.
-No. No. Mr. Yoon Dong-ju…
-Uh-uh, it's Mr. Jung.
Mr. Noh, I can't do it. I really can't.
[hisses]
-Yes, you can do it. Yes.
-[sighs] No.
Why do you even think
that you can't do it?
Stop having such weak thoughts. Come on.
You're a Murim girl
with endless potential, kid.
-Yeah.
-What does that even have to…
Oh. He's here. I'm leaving.
And get the job done, okay?
I'm watching you.
[chuckles]
Here's an easy one.
From these conditions,
we can derive two distinct equations.
-First, let's find the value of x…
-[sighs]
[Eui-ju] He'll kill me
if he discovers that I'm filming him
…the equation of this tangent line,
we can use it…
But then he's exposed the fact
that I write novels
after acting like he'd keep it a secret.
So let's just do it.
Mr. Ga.
I…
I have a question I'd like to ask.
What is it?
Uh…
Uh… Mr. Ga,
I heard you got faculty offers
from renowned overseas universities.
Why did you decide to teach here then?
Why are you asking this now?
Because I've thought about it
since you got here.
It's surprising a genius like you
chose to teach students here
so I'm wondering
if there's a story behind it.
I believe that's the type of question
you ask after class.
-Oh, come on.
-[groans]
-We wanna hear the story too.
-Yes, I'm curious too.
-If you tell us the story,
we'll study very hard!
[students chanting] Tell us now!
Tell us now!
-Tell us now! Tell us now!
-Quiet down.
All right. This story may actually
be of help to you
in deciding which career
to choose in life.
For the Olympiad,
they select six students that have to
go through two rounds of training camp.
On the day we arrived,
for the first round,
after checking in,
a test was already waiting for us.
That test… [sighs]
[gasps]
Take it out.
Take it out now.
[gasps]
[student] Wow… [whispers indistinctly]
Mr. Ga! Mr. Ga! Wait!
The Japanese language teacher said
all the teachers would get fired
if I didn't do it.
That's why I did it, Mr. Ga.
Mr. Ga, please hear me out this once.
I couldn't let
the teachers get fired, Mr. Ga.
Please hear me out, Mr. Ga. I…
Noh Da-ju, how could you use a student
to film me? Have you lost it?
Mr. Ga Woo-su, can you please calm down
so we can talk it out?
Someone filmed you
behind your back? [chuckles]
How could… [chuckles]
…someone ever do that?
Did you really have to shove a camera
in my face?
-You of all people?
-Guys, guys. Stop.
What's going on, huh?
Hey.
That was a long time ago.
You've gotta get over it.
You're still dwelling on that?
Hey! Hey, hey, hey! Hey!
[Young-hee] Mr. Ga Woo-su.
Could I have a moment with you?
[sighs]
Woo-su.
-[groans]
-You're unbelievable.
-Mr. Jung… [stammers]
-[sighs] This is nuts.
W-What is it?
Did something happen
to Mr. Ga in the past?
[sighs, clicks tongue]
I don't know the details.
But when Woo-su was ten,
after being on a TV show,
he ended up being stalked.
That darn stalker
would go to his school
and even to his house.
He filmed him without him knowing
what was going on.
It was a total mess.
Later on,
he kidnapped Woo-su.
Kidnapped him?
[Gi-jeon] It traumatized him.
[sighs]
Oh… [sighs]
[exhales sharply] Oh, dear. [whimpers]
-What's wrong?
-[whimpers]
[Young-hee] Mr. Ga Woo-su.
This is the real world.
People who know how to listen
survive longer
than those who think being smart
is enough to get by.
It's not like your face is going
to wear out just because we're filming it.
Stop making such a fuss.
-[inhales, sighs]
-[sighs]
Please excuse me.
If you're not willing to cooperate,
you leave me with no choice.
SUSPENSION NOTICE
YOON DONG-JU
I'm sure the other teachers
must have other options as well.
But it'll be quite tough
for Mr. Yoon Dong-ju
if he gets fired, right?
[Woo-su] Now, we can see that negative 4
is the average rate of change
in this equation.
Next, we need to find the f prime of x.
[chalk writing]
Two x minus three.
What's the average rate of change again?
[students] Negative four.
Yes, it's negative four.
He could have just agreed
to the filming from the start.
What was all that circus for?
My point exactly.
We're finishing late because of him.
-[Woo-su] Therefore, the value of x is…
-What the heck is this?
-So annoying.
-…is negative one-half.
And negative one-half is a number
that falls between negative three and two.
Therefore… [sighs] …c is…
[sighs]
We're finally done with it all.
CHAPTER 25: I ONLY FEEL BETRAYED
BECAUSE I TRUSTED YOU
[chuckles]
[snores]
[yawns]
[groaning]
[gasps] Auntie!
What… What am I doing here?
You said you couldn't sleep
at all last night
and wanted to get rest.
Were you asleep all along?
I… I was?
That makes no sense.
And the show?
They're done filming it all.
What?
[exclaims] Oh, no.
[exclaims] Oh, no!
No. No. Don't go. No. Please.
Auntie, they're leaving.
They're actually leaving.
They're leaving!
No!
[flute playing]
[sighs]
Just stop that!
[whimpers]
[groans, sniffles]
M-Mr. Ga.
[breathes shakily]
Mr. Ga.
[breathes shakily] Well…
Mr. Ga, I'm so sorry.
I would have never taken a video of you
if I had known what you went through.
I mean,
I shouldn't have done it regardless.
I'm so sorry.
It's my fault. I'm very, very sorry.
[exhales sharply]
You asked me a question during class.
Guess what crossed my mind
in that split second.
"Is she finally interested in math?"
After hearing your question, I thought,
"She may start with something unrelated.
Maybe she'll gain
a little bit of interest in math
once she hears
what I've been through in life."
So I tried to give you an earnest answer.
But you…
[sighs]
I felt let down
because I put my trust in you.
Forget it. Go home.
Sorry for letting you down.
I'm really sorry. [breathes shakily]
Go.
[breathes shakily]
[winces]
[groans]
[whimpers]
Get up.
Your act isn't going to work.
[Eui-ju inhales sharply]
[grunting]
[wincing]
Eui-ju.
Eui-ju. Eui-ju.
Wake up, Eui-ju!
Eui-ju.
[Eui-ju breathing heavily]
[whimpering]
[somber music playing]